<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>💥🔥📘</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://journal.henrykaufman.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://journal.henrykaufman.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 18:03:31 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 18:03:31 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starting Fresh</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m starting fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I have no idea what this means.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I do know a few things about what’s going on. Let’s talk about them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;clients&quot;&gt;Clients&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The past few months have been a blur to me. It’s been a pretty insane grind, but it’s all been worth it. Balancing this with other commitments becomes a burden, but it’s something that I have a passion for and I really don’t mind. I’ve been enjoying work more than ever, and it’s great to be able to move some Trello cards after a boring day at school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;school&quot;&gt;School&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My family moved. A new school. For anyone that’s pretty terrifying. It can also be very rewarding, and you can use it to your advantage. For example, new friends. I’ve fit myself into a totally different group of friends at my new high school. Not to discredit my old friends, but sometimes a change can be interesting. At the same time, it can also be little depressing. I miss many of the friends that I had at my old school. Even though I still live only a 45 minute drive away from my old house, I still find it frustrating that I can’t spend more time with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moving&quot;&gt;Moving&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moving has been awesome—to say the least. It’s been quite a change, but honestly that change is for the better. I’ve moved into much closer proximity to downtown Denver which makes working downtown on the weekends a breeze. Where I used to live, it was difficult to get around without a car, just because of the fact that it’s suburb. Here, I can bike or ride a bus almost everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the recap, but I can’t honestly tell you much about how things may or may not end up. All I can tell you is that it’s going to be an interesting journey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let’s begin.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 01:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://journal.henrykaufman.me/2016/10/20/fresh/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://journal.henrykaufman.me/2016/10/20/fresh/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
